http://www.online-educa.com/privacy-policy

Who We Are
Registered Company Name: OEB Learning Technologies Europe GmbH
Registration Number: HRB 81670
Registered Address:
Information We Collect
OEB Learning Technologies Europe GmbH collects:
Data submitted to us by the data subject, including:
Data submitted through our web forms (including registration forms)
Data collected onsite during our exhibition(s), this includes personal information and activities
Data collected by employees when in direct communication with persons / organisations
Information collected may include personal contact details, professional experience, demographics relating to your professional activity / interests, dietary requirements and communication preferences.
Data from third party sources, including:
Personal information or supplementary information from partners who we engage with in joint marketing efforts
Public data sources used to supplement or validate our existing datasets
Data services / suppliers used to obtain or supplement our existing datasets
Data which has been acquired as part of an acquisition or merger
Data gathered by automated technologies / services, including:
Data gathered from services which use IP address to determine which organisation visitors to our site originate from
Information from actions made by an individuals in response to direct marketing campaigns, including when an individual opens any emails or follows any links originating from our email communications
Information related to website navigation and usage
Data used to provide personalised marketing / user experiences while visiting our sites
Information We May Share
How data is shared within CloserStill
Your information may be shared with divisions within the CloserStill Media group of companies (list available here).
How we share your data with third parties
OEB Learning Technologies Europe GmbH may share your information with 3rd parties if:
You have consented to the sharing of this information:During registration
During form submission
While attending one of our events, in particular when attending theatres and visiting stands
Data sharing is required for us to fulfil a contractual obligation we have with you / your organisation
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation
You have consented to us sharing your details with carefully selected third parties whose products and services may interest you
We or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets
How We Process Your Information
We may use your personal information to:
Provide you with information and updates relating to a service you have signed up to
Ensure you can manage any service that you have signed up to
Deliver targeted promotional messaging relating to our services
Deliver targeted messaging relating to products and services of our affiliates (exhibitors, sponsors, media partners)
Invite you to take surveys related to our products or the products or our affiliates
Respond to you in relation to any enquiries you may have
Produce analytics relating to your usage of our products and response to our marketing activities
Legitimate Interests
If you have previously attended one of our conferences or other events, subscribed to one of our services or we have made an assessment of your interests based on your profession or industry, then, in the absence of consent, the legal basis on which we have processed your data and communicated with you is legitimate interest. We have a legitimate interest in communicating with you in order to give you information regarding upcoming conferences or our other services. It is necessary for us to market our services in this way as there is no cost-effective alternative. In balancing our interests against yours, we take into consideration the facts that the amount of your personal data we process is minimal, that it is not sensitive data, that there is a minimal privacy impact and that you can easily opt out or unsubscribe at any time.
Your Rights
Your rights under the GDPR include the following:
The right at any time to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data
The right to make a subject access request to be informed of what personal data of yours we hold
The right to have your personal data rectified in the event that it is inaccurate or incomplete
The right to request the erasure of your personal data
The right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data, especially where the processing is carried out for direct marketing purposes.
The right to restrict the processing of your personal data
The right to data portability (i.e. transfer of your personal data to another organisation)
Your rights above can be exercised by contacting us and will be dealt with free of charge, we may require confirmation of your identity depending on your request.
Security
We take precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft and misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction through the use of appropriate technical and organisational measures. Certain areas of our websites may be password protected. If you are a user of our websites and have a password, you can help to preserve your privacy by ensuring that you do not share your password with anyone else.
We take steps to regularly validate the personal information we hold to ensure that the information is accurate and, where necessary, up to date. Information that is no longer required for any valid business purpose, and that we are not required to keep pursuant to any applicable law, will be routinely destroyed by secure means.
Sub-Processors
Below is a non-exhaustive list of our sub-processors and what they are used for. This list is subject to change:
Sub-processor Name
Nature of Processing
Website
Amazon Web Services
Storage
https://aws.amazon.com/
CircData
Delegate and Exhibitor Registration
Website Usage & Cookies
Our website uses cookies, a cookie is a small file which is stored as text locally on the computer or device. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide an improved user experience when you browse our website and use our services. More information about cookies.
How we use Cookies
Remember preferences which have been set
Retain searches which have been made
Remember when you have signed into our site
Track the success of our marketing campaigns
3rd Party Social Plugin Cookies
We have embedded 3rd party Plugins (widgets) from our official Social profiles such as Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn. It is our understanding that any cookies placed by these sites are placed only when you visit these websites or sign-in to them via the plugins on our website. To find out more please review their respective cookie policies:
Facebook
LinkedIn
Twitter
Pinterest
Instagram
3rd Party Multimedia Cookies
We may choose to embed videos from Youtube, Vimeo, FlickR and other media services. Playing this content may set cookies on your computer. More information about how these services use cookies can be found below:
Youtube
Vimeo
Flickr
Other 3rd Party Cookies
We use 3rd party services to:
Track your usage of our site via Google Analytics©
Deliver targeted content via Feathr
Identify information relating to your organisation (Lead Forensics)
